https://www.darlingsdownunder.com.au/privacy-policy.htm

Shop by brand
NappiesAll-in-One NappiesBaby BeehindsGroVia All In OnePeekaboo (Pikapu) NappiesThirsties One Size All-In-OneBubblebubs AIO NappiesAll-in-Two/Snap-In NappiesBare and BohoEcoNapsPeekaboo (Pikapu) NappiesBaby BareBambooty BasicsBubblebubs CandiesDesigner BumsGrovia All-in-2 HybridBaby BeehindsPocket NappiesSeedling BabyEcoNapsRAWr NappiesThirsties Pocket NappiesDesigner Bums NappiesBaby Beehinds Magic-Alls MultifitsFitted NappiesBaby BareRAWr NappiesBaby BeehindsBubblebubsPrefold & Square/Flat NappiesGroVia PrefoldsSeedling Baby DiversifoldsNature's Child Organic Cotton NappiesBig Softies Flat NappiesBubblebubs Flats & PrefoldsMukti Organic PrefoldsNight NappiesOrganic NappiesOne Size Fits Most NappiesFitted - One SizePocket - One SizeAll-in-One - One SizeAll-in-2 - One SizePremmie & Newborn NappiesAll-in-2 Newborn NappiesPackagesPrefoldsFitted Newborn NappiesAll-in-One Newborn NappiesAussie Made Or Owned NappiesAussie Made/Owned- FittedAussie Made/Owned- PocketsAussie Made/Owned-AIOsAussie Made/Owned- All-in-2sPUL Nappy CoversSeedling Baby Comodo WrapRAWr Nappy CoversBaby Bare CoversBaby Beehinds CoversThirsties CoversThirsties Sized CoversThirsties Duo WrapsBubblebubs CoversFleece & Wool CoversBoosters & InsertsSwim NappiesPackagesCloth Nappy Starter PacksBaby Bare PackagesBaby Beehinds PackagesBambooty PackagesBare and Boho PackagesBubblebubs PackagesEcoNaps PackagesGroVia PackagesPeekaboo (Pikapu) PackagesSeedling Baby PackagesSuper Undies PackagesThirsties Nappy PackagesToilet Training ProductsCloth Nappies for Older ChildrenTraining PantsBedwetter/Night TrainersMattress ProtectorsCar Seat ProtectorsWet Bags & Pail LinersWetbagsLarge Hanging WetbagsWipes WetbagsPail/Bucket LinersNappy AccessoriesLinersCloth WipesWipes SolutionsNappy SprayersChange MatsSnappi'sBalms & LotionsWool AccessoriesNappy Repair KitsBaby ItemsFor Mum/Breastfeeding & PregnancyNursing Items & Breast PadsBreast PadsNursing & Breastfeeding ItemsCloth PadsBaby Beehinds Cloth PadsTwinkle Lily Cloth PadsSlings & CarriersLaundry & HomeEco DisposablesGift VouchersON SALE
My basket
Shopping info
Rewards program
Gift vouchers
Payment & postage
Layby
Returns Policy
Wholesale enquiries
menu
SHOP BY BRANDAffenzahnBaby BareBaby BeehindsBambootyBare and BohoBellelis AustraliaBig SoftiesBrolly SheetsBubblebubsBumGeniusCheeky WipesDarlings DownunderDesigner BumsEcoNapsGroViaJack n' JillLittle SquirtMuktiNature's ChildPeekaboo (Pikapu)RAWr NappiesSeedling BabySnappiStrucketSuper UndiesThirstiesTwinkle Lily
NappiesAll-in-One NappiesBaby BeehindsGroVia All In OnePeekaboo (Pikapu) NappiesThirsties One Size All-In-OneBubblebubs AIO NappiesAll-in-Two/Snap-In NappiesBare and BohoEcoNapsPeekaboo (Pikapu) NappiesBaby BareBambooty BasicsBubblebubs CandiesDesigner BumsGrovia All-in-2 HybridBaby BeehindsPocket NappiesSeedling BabyEcoNapsRAWr NappiesThirsties Pocket NappiesDesigner Bums NappiesBaby Beehinds Magic-Alls MultifitsFitted NappiesBaby BareRAWr NappiesBaby BeehindsBubblebubsPrefold & Square/Flat NappiesGroVia PrefoldsSeedling Baby DiversifoldsNature's Child Organic Cotton NappiesBig Softies Flat NappiesBubblebubs Flats & PrefoldsMukti Organic PrefoldsNight NappiesOrganic NappiesOne Size Fits Most NappiesFitted - One SizePocket - One SizeAll-in-One - One SizeAll-in-2 - One SizePremmie & Newborn NappiesAll-in-2 Newborn NappiesPackagesPrefoldsFitted Newborn NappiesAll-in-One Newborn NappiesAussie Made Or Owned NappiesAussie Made/Owned- FittedAussie Made/Owned- PocketsAussie Made/Owned-AIOsAussie Made/Owned- All-in-2sPUL Nappy CoversSeedling Baby Comodo WrapRAWr Nappy CoversBaby Bare CoversBaby Beehinds CoversThirsties CoversThirsties Sized CoversThirsties Duo WrapsBubblebubs CoversFleece & Wool CoversBoosters & InsertsSwim NappiesPackagesCloth Nappy Starter PacksBaby Bare PackagesBaby Beehinds PackagesBambooty PackagesBare and Boho PackagesBubblebubs PackagesEcoNaps PackagesGroVia PackagesPeekaboo (Pikapu) PackagesSeedling Baby PackagesSuper Undies PackagesThirsties Nappy PackagesToilet Training ProductsCloth Nappies for Older ChildrenTraining PantsBedwetter/Night TrainersMattress ProtectorsCar Seat ProtectorsWet Bags & Pail LinersWetbagsLarge Hanging WetbagsWipes WetbagsPail/Bucket LinersNappy AccessoriesLinersCloth WipesWipes SolutionsNappy SprayersChange MatsSnappi'sBalms & LotionsWool AccessoriesNappy Repair KitsBaby ItemsFor Mum/Breastfeeding & PregnancyNursing Items & Breast PadsBreast PadsNursing & Breastfeeding ItemsCloth PadsBaby Beehinds Cloth PadsTwinkle Lily Cloth PadsSlings & CarriersLaundry & HomeEco DisposablesGift VouchersON SALE
I just wanted to thank you for your prompt response to my queries; it gave me confidence to go ahead with buying online from your shop...I placed my order on Tuesday morning, it was packaged and despatched by Tuesday afternoon, and I received my first fluffy mail on Thursday, all through regular postage! I can't wait to try them out as a mum-to-be, expecting our firstborn in December this year.
Thanks for making this online shopping experience so pleasant for me - with your great customer service, super-quick postage and really lovely products!Ai Shin, August 2010more testimonials
Darlings Downunder Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important
Darlings Downunder is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. We comply with our obligations under the Australian Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) in respect of the collection, use, management, disclosure, quality, security, access and correction of your personal information.
Darlings Downunder is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites or businesses who may be referenced or linked on our website.
Why we collect & how we use information
To process an order and send it to you, and keep you up to date with your order status, we need to know your name, email address, delivery address, phone number and credit card details (for credit card payments).
We may also use your information to:
- answer enquiries and provide information or advice;
- provide you with your own account on our website to manage your purchases/gift registry;
- provide layby services, refunds, discounts and to process returns/exchanges;
- send you our newsletter or other news & offers we believe you will be interested in. If you do not wish to receive these communications you can opt-out by emailing us, or by clicking the 'opt out' link in our newsletter.
- better understand our customers’ needs and preferences;
- conduct product & market research;
- administer promotions/competitions, marketing activities, database compilation, analysis of trends and demographics and other marketing or promotional activities;
- protect against fraud and theft;
- internal record keeping;
- complete other transactions with you;
- maintain and update our records.
What information do we collect?
Generally, the information we collect about customers includes information to process and send you your order (your name, billing & delivery addresses, phone number, payment details (including credit card information) and e-mail addresses), or to send you our newsletter (email address).
We also collect details of the products you have purchased from us, so you can access your order history.
When you visit our website, we may also collect information including your IP address. We also collect some information that is not personal information because it does not identify you or anyone else, such as combined data about how users use our website or your postcode. This information is not converted into personal information.
We may also collect information about your use of our website using cookies. When you access our website, we may send a 'cookie' (which is a small summary file containing a unique ID number) to your computer. A cookie does NOT provide us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the information you choose to share with us.  We use cookies to measure traffic patterns, to determine which areas of our website have been visited and to measure transaction patterns as a whole. We use this to research our users’ habits so that we can improve our website and provide better customer service. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can set your browser so that your computer does not accept them. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
We also collect personal information from our suppliers about their products and business.
How we collect & hold information
We collect your personal information from you directly when you purchase products from us, provide feedback to us, set up an account with us, sign up to our newsletter or communicate with us (email, phone, social media or in person).
We take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. No information is stored offshore. Our website servers are based in Australia. We use a secure server when you access your account or place an order. A Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encrypts all information you have entered before it is sent via the Internet to us. We maintain a current SSL Certificate.
We use eWay - a secure, Australian, PCI DSS compliant credit card facility integrated into our website  - to process our credit card payments. Darlings Downunder does NOT process the payment directly or store any credit card details on our system. eWay secure customer and credit card data using military–grade software and it's encrypted by Ingrian devices to offer the highest level of protection possible. eWay are tier one PCI DSS compliant, meaning they adhere to the highest security standards set by Visa and MasterCard.
How we might share your information
We will only disclose information about you to third parties if required by law, or to businesses who are responsible for parts of our service delivery – including delivery companies, and sometimes (in the case of warranty matters or troubleshooting) suppliers and manufacturers. Darlings Downunder will not divulge or sell your information to any other third parties ever.
In the case of overseas based customers, we may need to pass some of your personal information to organisations located overseas such as your local delivery company (so you receive your parcel!).
In special circumstances – for example, if we were to sell our business or part of our business – your information may be transferred to potential purchasers and their advisers as part of that sale.
Accessing & correcting your information and questions
You can request access to your information or that your information be corrected by emailing us.
You can opt-out of any communication with us, by emailing us, or by clicking the 'opt out' link in any newsletter email from us.
If you have a question about our Privacy Policy or wish to make a complaint about the way we have collected, used, held or disclosed your personal information, please email us.
If you wish to make a formal complaint, please make your complaint in writing to the address below. We will consider your complaint promptly and contact you to seek to resolve the matter. If we have not responded to you within a reasonable time, you are entitled under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) to make a complaint to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner.
Contact
Darlings Downunder - Privacy
PO Box 6130
Wantirna VIC 3152
Email (to unsubscribe, complain, access or correct information): admin@darlingsdownnder.com.au
Darlings Downunder. Site by Media Two.
